funny.com 2007-06-08

# Funny.com: Funny Jokes, Funny Pictures, Funny Videos

|  |  |   
---|---|---  
|  | 

**We will not give out your personal information, e.g. your email address, to anyone.**

Funny.com is committed to safeguarding your online privacy. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many features. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

This policy will let you know:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected
  2. What cookies are and how they are used
  3. How your information is used
  4. With whom your information may be shared
  5. What information do advertisers collect
  6. How you can access, update or delete your information
  7. What else you should know about your online privacy

* * *

| What personally identifiable information does Funny.com collect from me?  
---  
Funny.com collects your name and e-mail address when you first register on the site. Funny.com also asks for additional information through its registration form, including but not limited to your birth date, country, gender, etc.  
   
What are cookies and how does Funny.com use them?  
  
As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, Funny.com uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive.

We use cookies only to identify who you are so when you return to Funny.com, if you asked us to remember your password, you would not need to type your password to login.

In addition, we collect the Internet Protocol address of each visitor to our site, which is a number that can be used to identify your internet service provider, among other things. Mail sent from Funny.com includes IP addresses in outgoing mail message headers.

Advertising networks that serve ads onto Funny.com may also use their own cookies.  

How does Funny.com use my information?  
  
Funny.com's primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our site.

Funny.com also analyzes the demographic information on an aggregated basis. Funny.com may share this aggregated data with 3rd party advertisers or business partners. However, all information shared are non-personally-identifiable (i.e. no individual information is shared or disclosed).  

With whom does Funny.com share my information?  
  
As a general rule, Funny.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below.

_Third Party Data & Data in the Aggregate_: Under confidentiality agreements, Funny.com may match user information with third party data. Also, Funny.com discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, 45% of our users are female) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

_Other_ : Funny.com may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Funny.com's Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Funny.com's rights or property, other Funny.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Funny.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.  

What information do advertisers collect?  
  
Funny.com uses 3rd party ad servers to serve banner advertisements on the website. For most ads, a 3rd party cookie is placed on your computer. This information is used to serve more relevant ads on this website and other sites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services of interest to you. You may choose not to have this information shared ("opt-out") with 3rd party advertisers at their website. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

For more information on your privacy with 3rd party advertisers, please visit their Web sites:

What is Funny.com's policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information?  
  
You may edit your Funny.com Account Information at any time by using your email address and password.

If you don't want to visit Funny.com for a while, we suggest that you leave your account intact rather than deleting it. So if you do decide to visit Funny.com again in the future, your information will remain accessible to you. Since Funny.com does not share your personal information with anyone, there is no harm in leaving your account inactive.

Your Funny.com account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in not being able to track funnies you've read at Funny.com, funnies you've submitted at Funny.com, funnies you've bookmarked at Funny.com, as well as messages sent to and from other Funny.com members.  

What else should I know about my privacy?  
  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.  

Additional Information   
  
If you have additional questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please fill out our feedback form.

Also see...

  * [Federal Trade Commission](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/index.html) \- information from the Federal Trade Commission for consumers.
  * [Electronic Frontier Foundation (eff.org)](http://www.eff.org/) \- protect fundamental civil liberties, including privacy and freedom of expression in the arena of computers and the Internet.
  * [Electronic Privacy Information Center (epic.org)](http://www.epic.org/) \- focus public attention on emerging civil liberties issues and to protect privacy, the First Amendment, and constitutional values. See [EPIC Cookies Page](http://www.epic.org/privacy/internet/cookies/) for more information on cookies.
  * [Center for Democracy and Technology (CDT)](http://www.cdt.org/privacy/) \- seeking practical solutions to enhance free expression and privacy in global communications technologies.

Privacy Policy last updated August 14, 2005. 

|   
|  |
